>> Brian Holt: 因此我想让这个更灵活
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I wanna make this more flexible so
我可以有不同的名字我可以有不同的动物
that I can have a different name, I can
have a difference type of animal, and
我可以有不同的品种对吧
I can have a different breed, right?
所以我想做的就是把属性传给我们
So what I wanna do is I wanna pass
attributes into the pet component which we
就有点早看到这个 ID 的东西了，对吧 ?
kinda already saw a little bit
earlier with this ID thing, right?
这就是你把它变成 div 的方式
This is how you pass
it into like a div and
我们可以用同样的方法把信息传递给宠物组件
we can use the same methodology to pass
information into the pet component.
我要在这里做些什么我要用一个有 VS 码的多重光标
So what I'm gonna do here, I'm gonna
use multiple cursors with a VS code.
所以我要点击然后按住 Alt ，然后再点击它的下面。
So I'm gonna click and then hold alt,
and click again underneath it like that.
现在我可以在三个不同的地方写作
And now I can write in three
different places at once.
所以我要用逗号来
So I'm gonna hit comma, and
然后我就会成为一个叫卢娜的名字
then I'm gonna pass in a name which for
now is going to be Luna.
一只会成为一只狗的动物
A animal which is gonna be a dog and
这个品种会是灌洗的
the breed, which is gonna be lavanese.
然后我要把它重组好让它变得更容易
And then I'm gonna had that reorganized so
it's little bit easier to
读 >> Brian Holt: 好的，
read
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
所以现在这个信息被通过了。
so now this information
is being passed down.
现在我要改变这一切了他们不是所有 Luna
Now I'm gonna change this so
they're not all Luna.
让我们把这只小鸟从成长起来
Let's make this one my bird from growing
up, which who's name was Pepper, and
佩珀是个凤头鹦鹉
Pepper was a cockatiel.
我们要把这个名字命名为我朋友的猫
And we're gonna name this after
my friend's cat which is the most
我曾经听过一只叫 Doink的猫
amusing name I've ever heard for
a cat which is Doink.
多墨大部分都是瞎子
Doink is mostly blind, so
Doink 只是把墙和墙都挤到墙里，就叫了名字。
Doink just kind of runs into walls and
Doinks the wall, hence the name.
Doink 是一只猫和一只像流浪狗一样的品种
Doink is a cat and
the breeds like stray or mixed or
这样我们就能混进去了
something like that we'll go with mixed.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在所有这些信息都被传递给宠物
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so now all this
information is being passed into the pet
组件，但我们必须使用它，我们还没有在任何地方使用它。
component, but we have to use it,
we're not using it yet anywhere.
这就是它所掌握的信息和信息
So what this does is it
takes this information and
它把它作为一个叫做道具的参数
it passes it in as a parameter
here called props.
> > Brian Holt: 所以不要在这里说 Luna ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
instead of saying Luna here,
我想说的是 props.props.here ，就是 props.name。
I'm gonna say props.whatever I called
this here, which is props.name.
所以不要在这里说狗我要说道具
So instead of saying dog here,
I'm gonna say props
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Instead of saying dog here,
我要说我所谓的动物好吗
I'm gonna say props.animal
is what I called it, okay?
然后我就会说 props.props
And then here, I'm gonna say props.breed.
那么，我现在期待什么时候去看浏览器呢 ?
So now what do I expect to see
when I go look at the browser?
看起来应该是一样的
It's gonna look relatively the same,
除了我要 3 个宠物而不是 Luna 3 次对吧
except I'm gonna have three different
pets instead of Luna three times, right?
>> Brian Holt: 所以如果我刷新页面，你可以看到我有 Luna， Pepper，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So if I refresh the page,
you can see here that I have Luna, Pepper,
还有 Doink
and Doink.